peakdesign.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy | Peak Design Official Site

We hold the highest respect for your privacy at Peak Design and we know that you care how information about you is used and shared. This notice describes what information we collect from our website users and how we use it. **By visiting peakdesign.com, pkdsn.com, or giveashot.org, you are accepting the practices described within.**

The last thing we want to do is violate your right to privacy and/or annoy the living daylight out of you. Hence, we’ve made it easy to opt out of our newsletter and opt out of having your data collected when you visit our site.

Just submit [this form](https://goo.gl/forms/iEO75utYQGHsRTP03). If you have any questions at all about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at security@peakdesign.com.

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT & RETAIN?

## ORDER FULFILLMENT INFORMATION

When you purchase products through our website, we collect your name and shipping address, as well as phone number and email address. All of these pieces of information are necessary to ship your order. We do not share any of your contact information with anybody other than our third party order fulfillment vendors. We retain your shipping details and order history to enable us to provide you with future customer services like returns and warranty replacements. If you create a peakdesign.com account we store your account password, which you can reset or change at any time. Your password is only accessible by you and never by Peak Design employees or third parties.

## CREDIT CARD PROCESSING

Peak Design does not collect or store credit card information provided when making a purchase on our website. All credit card transactions are handled by our third party payment gateways and merchant services.

## WEBSITE ANALYTICS

We use Google Analytics to track the volume and type of traffic that comes to our website. When you access this website Google may collect information such as cookies, IP address, search keywords, session length, browser type, page views and number of visits. None of this information is personally identifiable, and is subject to Google’s Privacy Policy. You have the option to opt out of our Google Analytics by opting out in your [Ads Control Panel](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) or in the global [ad network privacy](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). You can also install the [Google Analytics Opt-out Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) in your browser.

## DIGITAL MARKETING & RETARGETING

We use a few different digital marketing services to create and display online ads for our products. As you browse peakdesign.com, these services use cookies to remember what products you viewed and clicked on. Our advertising partners then enable us us to present you with advertising based on your previous interaction with peakdesign.com. You might see Peak Design ads on other websites, on Facebook and Instagram, or while watching videos on Youtube or other platforms. This practice is called “retargeting.” We don’t collect any personally identifiable information about you (like name or email) until you make a purchase. We also don’t directly retain your digital marketing information—instead, that data is retained by our third party marketing services. You can opt out of having your data retained by these services [here](https://peakdesign.typeform.com/to/KO8hVm).

## CART ABANDONMENT EMAILS

We work with a third party cart abandonment marketing service. After you've added products to your cart and started the checkout process, we allow that service to collect some of the information that you type into those checkout fields. They collect and retain your email address and what was in your cart. They do not collect any of your payment information. The information collected is used to send an automated email if you do not complete the checkout process. This email contains a link for you to contact us in case there is anything we can help you with. You can opt out of having your data collected and retained by our cart abandonment service [here](https://peakdesign.typeform.com/to/KO8hVm).

## CUSTOMER SUPPORT

We use a third party service to host and manage our Support Center and Contact Us form. When you fill out the Contact Us form or email [info@peakdesign.com](mailto:info@peakdesign.com), our support service retains all of the information you provided, including your name and email. This information enables our support team to see a history of your support inquiries and provide you with the best possible service. Your customer service history is only accessible by the Peak Design Customer Service team.

## PEAK DESIGN NEWSLETTER

If you sign up or opt in to the [Peak Design Newsletter](http://eepurl.com/pq-oL) we will collect your name and email address for the purposes of sending you occasional updates about our company. We will never share or sell this information to anybody without your consent, and you can [unsubscribe](http://peakdesignltd.us5.list-manage1.com/unsubscribe?u=c0ab316ca267399dfb4e4fd7e&id=fc6ec9d62a) at any time.

## WEBSITE A/B TESTING

We’re always trying to make our website a better experience for customers. To do this, we use third party tools to run A/B tests. During an A/B test, we split our website visitors into 2 groups and show each group a different page design. We then analytical tools to determine which group of customers was best able to accomplish their goals on our site. The winning page design is then implemented for 100% of website visitors. Our A/B testing and analytical tools do not collect or retain personally identifiable information. Instead, they collect and retain pages you visit on our website, things you click on, mouse movements, and how far down you scroll. You can opt out of having your data collected and retained by these services [here](https://peakdesign.typeform.com/to/KO8hVm).

## How does Google Analytics work?

Google Analytics is Google’s web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how their visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics collects information anonymously, and much like examining footprints in sand, it reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. Analytics uses its own cookie to track visitor interactions. The cookie is used to store information, such as what time the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before, and what site referred the visitor to the web page. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve their website and how people find it. A different cookie is used for each website, and visitors are not tracked across multiple sites. Analytics requires that all websites that use it must update their privacy policy to include a notice that fully discloses the use of Analytics. To disable this type of cookie, some browsers will indicate when a cookie is being sent and allow you to decline cookies on a case-by-case basis. In addition to declining cookies, you can also install the [Google Analytics Opt-out Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) in your browser, which prevents Google Analytics from collecting information about your website visits.

## HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

Peak Design takes security seriously and cares about the integrity of your personal information. We use commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological methods to transmit and store your data in a secure, encrypted manner. However, Peak Design cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat our security measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

## DO WE SELL ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

No, we don’t. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## THIRD PARTY LINKS

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website or via our social media channels. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline or through other platforms or channels

## TERMS AND CONDITIONS

Please also visit our Legal Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

## YOUR CONSENT

By using our site, you consent to this web site privacy policy.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 5/24/2018

## CONTACTING US

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at security@peakdesign.com.
